Guide to the John M. Meek Collection
John M. Meek Collection 1934-1999 1967-1968
- Photographs, 1952-1993; id1099928; CAC_PP_068_4_0000_0000_0000
  - Daily Oklahoman's Washington, D.C. bureau chief Allan Cromley (left) and former NBC "Today Show" host Jim Hartz (right), 1993; id1100103; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_21b (Box 1)
  - John Meek with guest, 1993; id1100104; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_21c (Box 1)
  - Julian Rothbaum (second from the left) and John Meek (second from the right), 1993; id1100105; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_21d (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100106; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22a (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100107; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22b (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100108; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22c (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100109; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22d (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100110; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22e (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100111; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22f (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100112; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22g (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100113; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22h (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100114; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22i (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100115; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22j (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100116; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22k (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100117; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22l (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100118; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22m (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100119; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22n (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100120; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22o (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100121; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22p (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100122; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22q (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100123; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22r (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100124; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22s (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100125; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22t (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100126; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22u (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100127; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22v (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100128; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22w (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100129; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22x (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100130; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22y (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100131; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22z (Box 1)
  - Clinton/Gore Inaugural Event, 1993; id1100132; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_22aa (Box 1)
  - Mrs. Tom Petit, Tom Petit, Mary Dorman, and Bill Danoff, 1993; id1100133; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_23a (Box 1)
  - Jim Bohannon, 1993; id1100134; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_23b (Box 1)
  - Former Oklahoma Governor George Nigh (far right), 1993; id1100135; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_23c (Box 1)
  - Former Oklahoma first lady Donna Nigh, Jan Scruggs, and other guests, 1993; id1100136; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_23d (Box 1)
  - Tom Petit, Mrs. Tom Petit, Tulsa Attorney, Mary Dorman, and George Nigh, 1993; id1100137; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_23e (Box 1)
  - Bill Danoff and guest., 1993; id1100138; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_23f (Box 1)
  - Former first lady Donna Nigh facing camera, 1993; id1100139; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_23g (Box 1)
  - Guests, John Meek's Inaugural Party, 1993; id1100140; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_23h (Box 1)
  - DeeDee Myers, Press Aide, 1992; id1100141; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_24 (Box 1)
  - Ann Edwards, chief press advance person, 1992; id1100142; CAC_PP_068_4_1_0000_25 (Box 1)